So, the wedding caterers sent me this list
因此，婚禮餐飲服務商向我傳送了此列表
of 12 appetizers and I have to narrow
12 道開胃菜，我必須縮小範圍
it down to six.
減少到六。
Food?
食物？
Give me.
給我。
So, did Monica tell you about this great
那麼，莫妮卡有沒有告訴你這個偉大的事情？
band called the Swing Kings that we're trying
我們正在嘗試的樂團名為“搖擺之王”
to get to play for the wedding?
去參加婚禮嗎？
Since when are you into swing music?
你從什麼時候開始喜歡上搖擺樂的？
Since forever.
自永遠以來。
I used to go all over town listening
我曾經走遍全城聆聽
to bands.
到樂隊。
Chandler.
錢德勒。
Gaff commercial.
加夫廣告。
So, did you book them?
那麼，你預訂了嗎？
Did you call?
你打電話了嗎？
I will.
我會。
Do you want me to call?
你要我打電話嗎？
No, I'll do it.
不，我會做的。
You just stick to your job.
你只要堅持你的工作就好了。
What is your job?
你做什麼工作？
Staying out of the way.
不礙事。
This is impossible, Monica.
這是不可能的，莫妮卡。
Why don't you just pick off 15?
為啥不直接選15個呢？
There were only 12.
只有12個。
Oh, yeah, I added three.
哦，是的，我加了三個。
What are peanut butter fingers?
什麼是花生醬手指？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Well, hello.
嗯，你好。
She's cute.
她很可愛。
Should we go try to talk to her?
我們應該去嘗試和她談談嗎？
Sure.
當然。
It's one of the great things about being
這是存在的偉大事情之一
engaged.
已訂婚的。
I'm not nervous talking to pretty girls anymore.
和漂亮女孩說話我不再緊張了。
Could you guys help me?
你們能幫我嗎？
Yeah, let me get that for you.
是的，讓我拿給你。
It's really heavy.
真的很重。
I got it.
我得到了它。
So, hi, I'm Ross and this is my
所以，嗨，我是羅斯，這是我的
friend Chandler.
朋友錢德勒。
I'm Kristen.
我是克里斯汀。
Kristen, hi.
克里斯汀，嗨。
Are you new to the area?
您是該地區的新手嗎？
Because if you are, I'd love to show
因為如果你是，我很樂意展示
you around sometime.
有時間你在身邊。
I actually just moved from four blocks over.
事實上我剛從四個街區搬來。
But this block is like a whole other
但這個街區就像另一個街區一樣
world.
世界。
Actually, it does have a very interesting history.
事實上，它確實有一段非常有趣的歷史。
This street is the first street in the
這條街是全區第一條街
city to have an underground sewer system.
城市擁有地下排水系統。
Before that, sewage and waste would just flow
在此之前，汙水和廢棄物只會流動
right down the street.
就在街上。
Sometimes ankle deep.
有時深至腳踝。
Smooth.
光滑的。
Excuse me?
打擾一下？
Say, you're going to be starving after all
說吧，你終究會餓死的
this moving.
這個感動。
What do you say I take you to
你說什麼我帶你去
dinner tonight?
今晚吃晚餐嗎？
I'd like that.
我想要那樣。
Yeah?
是的？
Great.
偉大的。
Let me take this up for you.
讓我來替你解決這個問題。
After you.
您先請。
Oh, no, no.
哦，不，不。
After you.
您先請。
Oh my God!
我的天啊！
Am I crazy or does this totally go?
我瘋了還是這一切都過去了？
Oh my God, you look so beautiful.
天啊，你看起來真漂亮。
Thank you, Rachel, but look at Monica.
謝謝你，雷切爾，但看看莫妮卡。
This is it.
就是這樣。
This is the one.
就是這個。
I can't believe I found it.
我不敢相信我找到了它。
Wow, you look so beautiful.
哇，你看起來真漂亮。
If I knew you, I'd cry.
如果我認識你，我會哭。
Well, I'm Monica Geller, ball like a baby.
嗯，我是莫妮卡·蓋勒，像個嬰兒一樣活潑。
I'm Megan Bailey.
我是梅根·貝利。
Have you found your dress yet?
你找到你的衣服了嗎？
Oh, no.
哦，不。
These dresses are all so amazing, but there
這些衣服都太棒了，但是有
is no way I could afford one.
我根本買不起。
No, no, I can't afford this either.
不不不，我也買不起。
No, I'm just here to figure out which
不，我只是來弄清楚哪個
one I want.
我想要的一個。
Then I'm going to get it at Kleinman's,
然後我要去 Kleinman's 買
this discount place in Brooklyn.
布魯克林的這個折扣店。
Day after tomorrow, they're having a huge sale.
後天，他們就有大促銷。
Oh, thanks for the tip.
哦，謝謝你的提示。
Yeah.
是的。
So when are you getting married?
那你什麼時候結婚？
Oh, I'm not.
哦，我不是。
I just like to try these on.
我只是喜歡嘗試這些。
I do the same thing.
我也做同樣的事情。
I'm just kidding.
我只是在開玩笑。
I'm getting married July 25th.
我將於7月25日結婚。
I'm just kidding, too.
我也只是開玩笑。
I'm getting married in December.
我十二月就要結婚了。
So when are you getting married?
那你什麼時候結婚？
Oh, May 15th.
哦，5月15日。
Oh, it's getting close.
哦，已經很接近了。
Yeah.
是的。
So who's your photographer?
那你的攝影師是誰？
Jeffrey.
傑弗裡.
We met with him.
我們會見了他。
Did he show you the photos of the
他給你看照片了嗎？
nude wedding he did?
他舉辦裸體婚禮？
The best man?
最好的男人？
Wow.
哇。
I know.
我知道。
I almost called off my wedding.
我差點就取消了婚禮。
Oh, who's your band?
哦，你的樂團是誰？
Oh, my fiancé wants the Swing Kings.
哦，我的未婚夫想要搖擺之王。
Oh, you're so lucky.
哦，你真幸運。
My fiancé wants the heavy metal band Carcass.
我的未婚夫想要重金屬樂團 Carcass。
Oh, is that spelled with a C or
哦，這是用 C 拼寫的還是
a K?
一個K？
Oh my God, it doesn't matter.
天啊，沒關係。
They're both great.
他們都很棒。
Oh, you know what?
哦，你知道嗎？
You know what?
你知道嗎？
Don't buy that here.
不要在這裡買那個。
Now that you know what you want, you
既然你知道自己想要什麼，那你
should go to Kleinman's and you can get
應該去Kleinman's，你可以得到
it half off.
它半價。
This place is so overpriced.
這個地方太貴了。
I own this store.
我擁有這家商店。
So, does this come in another color or...?
那麼，它有其他顏色還是......？
Hi.
你好。
Are you moving in or moving out?
您要搬進來還是搬出去？
Moving in.
搬進來。
Oh, can I give you a hand?
哦，我可以幫你嗎？
Oh, okay.
哦好的。
But, you know, be careful because the guy
但是，你知道，要小心，因為那傢伙
who was helping me before had to leave
之前幫助我的人不得不離開
because he hurt his back.
因為他傷了背。
Boyfriend?
男朋友？
No.
不。
I'm Joey.
我是喬伊。
Hi.
你好。
Kristen.
克里斯汀.
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
What a beautiful name.
多麼美麗的名字。
What is it again?
又是什麼？
Kristen.
克里斯汀.
Ah, that's it.
啊，就是這樣。
Okay.
好的。
So, you live around here?
那麼，你住在這附近嗎？
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
Right down there.
就在那裡。
Listen, let me give you a little tip.
聽著，讓我給你一個小提示。
Do not take a nap on this stoop
不要在這個門廊上小睡
or you could wake up with your shoes
或者你可以帶著你的鞋子醒來
gone.
走了。
I'll remember that.
我會記住這一點。
Okay.
好的。
Hey, you know, listen.
嘿，你知道，聽著。
Would you, uh...
你願意嗎，呃…
Would you like to have dinner with me
你願意和我一起吃晚餐嗎
tonight?
今晚？
Oh, I have plans tonight.
哦，我今晚有計劃。
Oh.
哦。
But how about tomorrow?
但明天呢？
Sounds great.
聽起來很棒。
Okay, all right.
好吧，好吧。
Well, where does this go?
那麼，這會去哪裡呢？
You look strong.
你看起來很堅強。
Why don't I take that and you grab
為什麼我不拿走，而你抓住
one of the boxes?
其中一個盒子？
Okay.
好的。
Yeah.
是的。
It's taking so long.
花了這麼長時間。
I mean, forever.
我的意思是，永遠。
Shit.
拉屎。
Come on.
快點。
So, this is Brooklyn.
所以，這就是布魯克林。
All right, listen up.
好吧，聽著。
There's usually only one dress in each size.
通常每個尺寸只有一件衣服。
So, when they open those doors, fan out.
所以，當他們開啟這些門時，就散開。
Now, this is what you're looking for.
現在，這就是您正在尋找的。
Memorize it.
記住它。
When you locate the dress, blow on these,
當你找到那件衣服時，對著這些吹氣，
all right?
好的？
Three sharp blasts.
三聲尖銳的爆炸聲。
When you hear it, come running.
聽到了就趕快跑吧。
Got it.
知道了。
All right.
好的。
Oh, they're pushing.
哦，他們在推動。
Don't be a baby.
別像個嬰兒。
Let's go.
我們走吧。
Rachel, come on.
雷切爾，來吧。
No, no, not it, not it, not it.
不不不，不是這樣，不是這樣，不是這樣。
Don't crowd me.
別擠我。
This is it.
就是這樣。
This is the dress.
這就是這件衣服。
Oh, my God, it's perfect.
哦，天哪，太完美了。
I'm sorry, this one's taken.
抱歉，這張已被佔用。
Whoa.
哇哦。
Megan.
梅根。
Monica.
莫妮卡。
You came.
你來了。
Yeah.
是的。
This is my dress.
這是我的衣服。
No.
不。
Yes, it is.
是的。
You saw me wearing it.
你看到我穿著它了。
And now you'll see me buying it.
現在你會看到我買它。
What?
什麼？
You freak.
你這個怪胎。
You wouldn't even have known about this place
你甚至不會知道這個地方
if it wasn't for me.
如果不是我的話。
Look, you don't want to fight me.
聽著，你不想跟我戰鬥。
Maybe I do.
也許我會。
I'm pretty feisty.
我還蠻囂張的
I'm coming, I'm coming.
我來了，我來了。
Okay.
好的。
Hey, what do I do?
嘿，我該怎麼辦？
Did you find the dress?
你找到那件衣服了嗎？
No, you've got to get me out of
不，你必須讓我離開
here, Phoebe.
在這裡，菲比。
These bargain shoppers are crazy.
這些討價還價的購物者太瘋狂了。
You've got to get Monica.
你必須得到莫妮卡。
You've got to hold my hand.
你必須握住我的手。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Excuse me.
打擾一下。
Go, go, go.
去！去！去。
Go.
去。
So, Ross, how was your date the other
那麼，羅斯，你的約會物件呢？
night?
夜晚？
Did you tell her about the magical ride
你告訴她關於神奇之旅的事了嗎
that starts with the flush of every toilet?
從每個廁所的沖水開始？
Laugh all you want, but she actually left
你想笑就笑，她卻真的離開了
me a message saying she'd like to go
傳訊息給我說她想去
out again.
又出來了。
Huh.
呵呵。
In fact, I'm going to go call her
事實上，我要去給她打電話
right now.
現在。
And I'll make sure to tell her my
我一定會告訴她我的
friend Chandler says...
朋友錢德勒說…
Hey, Jim.
嘿，吉姆。
Hey.
嘿。
Listen, sorry I didn't stop by last night,
聽著，抱歉我昨晚沒有過來，
but I had a date.
但我有個約會。
Joe, when it's one o'clock in the
喬，現在是凌晨一點
morning and you don't come by, that's okay.
早上你沒來，沒關係。
Check it out.
一探究竟。
It was with this really hot girl who
正是和這個非常性感的女孩一起
just moved in right across the street.
剛搬到街對面。
Really?
真的嗎？
Right across the street?
就在街對面嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
When'd you meet her?
你什麼時候認識她的？
Two days ago.
兩天前。
Excellent.
出色的。
You know, Ross met somebody, too.
你知道，羅斯也遇過一個人。
What?
什麼？
Hey.
嘿。
Hi, how'd it go?
嗨，怎麼樣？
Oh, great.
哦，太好了。
We're going out again Saturday.
週六我們又要出去了。
But I just found out she's also seeing
但我剛發現她也看到了
some other guy.
另一個人。
Really?
真的嗎？
Joe, what would you do if you were
喬，如果你是你，你會怎麼做？
in Ross' situation?
羅斯的情況呢？
Well, I sort of am.
嗯，我有點是。
I mean, yeah, I'm dating this girl who's
我的意思是，是的，我正在和這個女孩約會
also seeing another guy, but I'm not too
也看到了另一個男人，但我不太喜歡
worried about it.
擔心它。
Well, you shouldn't be.
嗯，你不應該這樣。
Believe me, I wouldn't want to be the
相信我，我不想成為
guy who's up against you.
與你作對的人。
I mean, that doofus is going to lose.
我的意思是，那個傻瓜會輸的。
So, this is nice.
所以，這很好。
I wish I didn't have to go.
我希望我不必去。
Believe me.
相信我。
But unfortunately, I have to.
但不幸的是，我不得不這麼做。
Oh, by the way, what's the name of
哦，順便問一下，叫什麼名字
the girl you're dating?
你正在約會的那個女孩？
Kristen Leigh.
克里斯汀·利.
Bye.
再見。
Well, obviously only one of us can keep
好吧，顯然只有我們可以保留
dating her.
和她約會。
Obviously.
明顯地。
So how do we decide?
那我們該如何決定呢？
Well, now, let's look at this objectively.
好吧，現在讓我們客觀地看待這個問題。
I think I should date her.
我想我應該和她約會。
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
嗯嗯，嗯嗯。
Or, or I'm the one who dates her.
或者，或者我是和她約會的人。
That's interesting.
那很有意思。
But check this out.
但看看這個。
I date her.
我和她約會。
Yeah, yeah, I like that.
是的，是的，我喜歡這樣。
But just to go in another direction.
但只是為了走向另一個方向。
Okay, okay.
好吧，好吧。
This can go on for a while.
這種情況可能會持續一段時間。
Yeah, well, we should order some food, don't
是的，好吧，我們應該點些食物，不要
we?
我們？
No, Joey.
不，喬伊。
Look, why don't, why don't we just let
聽著，為什麼不，為什麼我們不讓
her decide?
她決定嗎？
Okay?
好的？
Hey, hey, we'll each go out with her
嘿嘿嘿，我們兩個一起出去吧
one more time.
再一次。
And, and we'll see who she likes best.
而且，我們會看看她最喜歡誰。
That sounds fair.
聽起來很公平。
Maybe I'll take her to that new French
也許我會帶她去嘗試新的法語
restaurant down the street.
街上的餐廳。
Hey, wait a second now.
嘿，等一下。
Look, we're going to have to set a
聽著，我們必須設定一個
spending limit on the date.
當日消費限額。
I don't have the money to take her
我沒有錢帶她
to a fancy place like that.
到那樣一個奇特的地方。
Well, sorry.
好吧，抱歉。
That's what I do on dates.
這就是我在約會時所做的事情。
All right.
好的。
Well, I guess I'll just have to do
好吧，我想我只需要這樣做
what I do on dates.
我在約會時做什麼。
So let's decide on a spending limit.
因此，讓我們決定支出限額。
Yeah.
是的。
A slice.
一片。
Six dollars.
六美元。
I was thinking more like a hundred.
我想更像是一百個。
Okay.
好的。
And I bought her 94 dollars.
我買了94美元給她。
Oh, I know.
哦，我知道。
Can you hand me a tissue?
你能給我一張紙巾嗎？
You're out of Diet Coke.
你的健怡可樂已經用完了。
Hello?
你好？
What?
什麼？
You what?
你什麼？
Hey, you listen here, missy.
嘿，你聽著，小姐。
What?
什麼？
That was that girl, Megan.
那就是那個女孩，梅根。
She booked the Swing Kings on the day
她當天預訂了搖擺王
of our wedding and said I couldn't have
我們的婚禮並說我不能
them back unless I gave her the dress.
除非我把衣服給她，否則他們就會回來。
Oh!
哦！
Does that mean carcass is available?
這是否意味著屍體可用？
What am I going to do?
我要做什麼？
That is the dress.
那就是這件衣服。
Oh.
哦。
But Chandler wants the band.
但錢德勒想要樂團。
I don't...
我不...
What do I do?
我該怎麼辦？
Well, just figure out a way to talk
好吧，想個辦法談談
him out of it.
他擺脫了它。
How?
如何？
You're out of toilet paper!
你的衛生紙沒了！
Hey.
嘿。
What's up?
這是怎麼回事？
I just wanted to come by and, you
我只是想過來，而你
know, wish you good luck on your date.
知道了，祝你約會好運。
Oh, thanks.
哦，謝謝。
Yeah.
是的。
What time are you meeting her?
你幾點見她？
We have 8 o'clock reservations at Gramercy
我們有 8 點在 Gramercy 的預訂
Bistro.
小酒館。
Well, that's in like 20 minutes.
嗯，大概 20 分鐘就到了。
You better get dressed.
你最好穿好衣服。
I am dressed.
我穿好衣服了。
Oh.
哦。
Well, good.
嗯，很好。
For me.
為我。
What is this?
這是什麼？
Did you give yourself a facial?
你為自己做了臉部護理嗎？
I have an oily T-zone.
我的T區很油。
Okay, dude.
好吧，夥計。
Hey, you sent Kristen Flowers?
嘿，你送了克莉絲汀‧弗勞爾斯嗎？
That's right.
這是正確的。
You spent $100.
你花了 100 美元。
That's the limit.
這就是極限。
You're screwed.
你完蛋了。
Actually, I sent the flowers before the actual
事實上，我在實際之前就送了花
date.
日期。
So, technically...
所以，從技術上來說...
Technically, I didn't break any rules.
從技術上講，我沒有違反任何規則。
Thanks for stopping by, though.
不過還是謝謝你過來。
Oh, so that's the way it's gonna be,
哦，事情就是這樣，
huh?
嗯？
Yeah, I can break the rules, too, you
是的，我也可以違反規則，你
know.
知道。
Oh, yeah?
哦，是嗎？
What are you gonna do?
你要做什麼？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Why am I not surprised?
為什麼我不感到驚訝？
You know what, Ross?
你知道嗎，羅斯？
I'm not gonna let you get away with
我不會讓你逃脫
this.
這。
I don't think you have much choice.
我認為你沒有太多選擇。
Oh, we'll see.
哦，我們拭目以待。
Bye-bye.
再見。
Yeah, bye-bye.
是的，再見。
Hey.
嘿。
So, just a light layer?
那麼，只是一個光層？
Yeah, just...
是的，只是...
Here and there.
這裡和那裡。
Joey got meat sauce on the banister again.
喬伊的欄桿上又沾上了肉醬。
Yeah, swing music is so out.
是啊，搖擺樂太過時了。
Phoebe, he's gotta be in the room for
菲比，他必須待在房間裡
that to work.
那個工作。
What are you guys talking about?
你們在說什麼？
Well, um, we were just talking about the,
嗯，嗯，我們剛才正在談論，
you know, the swing kings and just wondering
你知道，搖擺之王，只是想知道
whether, you know, they were the right way
你知道，他們的方式是否正確
to go.
去。
Yeah, I went to a wedding once where
是的，我參加過一次婚禮
they had swing music and, uh, two months
他們有搖擺樂，呃，兩個月
later, the couple got divorced.
後來，夫妻倆離婚了。
And, no, I'm not saying that there's any
而且，不，我並不是說有任何
connection here, you know, but they did tell
這裡有聯絡，你知道，但他們確實告訴了
me that's why they got divorced.
我這就是他們離婚的原因。
But I love swing music.
但我喜歡搖擺樂。
Yeah, but the swing kings, you know, they
是的，但是搖擺之王，你知道，他們
suck so much that people actually die at
太爛了以至於人們實際上死了
their concerts.
他們的音樂會。
They just stop living.
他們只是停止生活。
All I know is when Monica and I
我只知道當莫妮卡和我
went to see them, we had fun and
去看他們，我們玩得很開心
there's another reason, too.
還有另一個原因。
Well, what is the other reason?
那麼，還有什麼原因呢？
I don't want to say.
我不想說。
Well, you have to because maybe it's stupid.
好吧，你必須這樣做，因為也許這很愚蠢。
Well, it's just while Monica and I were
嗯，就在莫妮卡和我在一起的時候
dancing to them, it was the first time
給他們跳舞，這是第一次
I knew that you were the woman that
我知道你就是那個女人
I wanted to dance all my dances with.
我想和我一起跳我所有的舞蹈。
Oh, crap.
哦，糟糕。
So, they said our table will be ready
所以，他們說我們的桌子已經準備好了
in just a few minutes.
只需幾分鐘。
Oh, great.
哦，太好了。
Is your back feeling better?
你的背部感覺好些了嗎？
Oh, yeah, that's fine.
哦，是的，那很好。
I guess the more muscles you have, the
我猜你的肌肉越多
more they can spasm out of control.
更多的時候他們會痙攣失控。
Kristen?
克里斯汀？
Joey!
喬伊！
Hi.
你好。
What are you doing here?
你在這裡做什麼？
Oh, I like this place.
哦，我喜歡這個地方。
Yeah.
是的。
And you?
你呢？
Technically.
從技術上來說。
I'm not breaking any rules, so...
我沒有違反任何規則，所以...
Ross, this is Joey.
羅斯，這是喬伊。
Joey?
喬伊？
Ross.
羅斯.
Hi.
你好。
It's nice to meet you.
很高興認識你。
I used to have a friend named Joey.
我曾經有一個朋友，名叫喬伊。
I don't anymore.
我不再這樣了
Our table will be ready in a couple
我們的桌子將準備好
minutes, so...
分鐘，所以...
Yeah, so...
是的，所以...
Sure, I would love to wait with you
當然，我很願意和你一起等待
guys.
夥計們。
Thanks.
謝謝。
So, Joey, you look familiar.
所以，喬伊，你看起來很眼熟。
Are you on TV or something?
你在電視上嗎？
Well, Joey doesn't like to talk about it,
好吧，喬伊不喜歡談論這個，
but he's one of the stars of Days
但他是《Days》的明星之一
of Our Lives.
我們的生活。
That's right.
這是正確的。
Don't you play a woman?
你不演女人嗎？
A woman in a man's body.
一個女人住在一個男人的身體裡。
Much better.
好多了。
So, you know, Ross, it's funny, because you
所以，你知道，羅斯，這很有趣，因為你
look familiar to me, too.
我也覺得很眼熟。
Have you ever been married?
你結過婚嗎？
Well, yes, yes, I have.
嗯，是的，是的，我有。
In fact, just the other day, Kristen and
事實上，就在前幾天，克里斯汀和
I were talking about how I've been married
我正在談論我是如何結婚的
and how I have a son.
以及我如何擁有一個兒子。
Yeah, little Eric.
是的，小艾裡克。
That's right.
這是正確的。
Wait, no, Ben.
等等，不，本。
So you've just been married the one time,
所以你才剛結婚一次
then?
然後？
Well, um...
嗯，嗯...
You've been married twice?
你結過兩次婚嗎？
Yes.
是的。
And...
還有...
another time after that.
之後還有一次。
Boy, I'm getting hungry.
男孩，我餓了。
Uh, hey, Joey, have you ever been so
呃，嘿，喬伊，你曾經這樣嗎
hungry on a date that when the girl
約會時餓了，當女孩
goes to the bathroom, you ate some of
去洗手間，你吃了一些
her food?
她的食物？
You said the waiter ate my crab cake.
你說服務生吃了我的蟹餅。
Yeah.
是的。
So, uh, Ross, now, why did that first
所以，呃，羅斯，現在，為什麼首先這樣做
marriage break up?
婚姻破裂？
Hmm?
唔？
Was it because the woman was straight or
是因為這個女人是異性戀還是
because she was a lesbian?
因為她是女同性戀？
Do you two know each other?
你們兩個認識嗎？
No.
不。
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
It just seems like Ross is the kind
看來羅斯就是這樣的人
of guy who would marry a woman on
願意娶女人的男人
the verge of being a lesbian and then
即將成為女同性戀，然後
push her over the edge.
把她推到邊緣。
Uh...
呃...
Wait a minute.
等一下。
Were you on a poster for gonorrhea?
你出現在淋病海報上嗎？
You ever slept in the same bed with
你曾經和你睡在同一張床上
a monkey?
一隻猴子？
Hey, you leave Marcel out of this.
嘿，你把馬塞爾排除在外了。
All right, you ever got stuck in a
好吧，你曾經陷入過困境
pair of your own leather pants?
一條你自己的皮褲？
Hey, hey, have you ever locked yourself in
嘿嘿嘿你有沒有把自己鎖在裡面
a TV cabinet, V.D. Boy?
電視櫃，V.D.男生？
Monkey lover!
猴子愛好者！
Where do you think we lost her?
你認為我們在哪裡失去了她？
Probably around gonorrhea.
可能是淋病左右。
Geller, table of two.
蓋勒，兩人桌。
You hungry?
你餓了嗎？
There's a bear shit in the woods.
樹林裡有熊屎。
Hi, honey, I'm home.
嗨，親愛的，我回來了。
Don't come in here.
別進來。
Why?
為什麼？
Do you have another boyfriend in there or
你裡面還有別的男友嗎？
something?
某物？
No.
不。
We only mess around in his place.
我們只是代替他亂搞而已。
You know, it's funny.
你知道，這很有趣。
I started it, but now it's scaring me,
我一開始就是這樣，但現在讓我害怕了
so could you come out here, please?
那你能出來一下嗎？
No, I'm wearing a wedding dress.
不，我穿著婚紗。
Oh, you got a wedding dress?
哦，你有婚紗嗎？
That's great.
那太棒了。
Yeah, but I'm not keeping it.
是的，但我不會保留它。
Well, then why can't I see it?
嗯，那為什麼我看不到呢？
Oh, I guess you can.
哦，我想你可以。
Okay, but I have to return it, so
好的，但我必須退貨，所以
you can't like it.
你不能喜歡它。
Okay, I promise I'll hate it.
好吧，我保證我會討厭它。
Wow, you look hideous.
哇，你看起來很醜。
Really?
真的嗎？
Yeah, that's like the most ugliest dress I've
是的，這就像我穿過的最難看的衣服
ever seen.
曾經見過。
Why do you have to return it?
為什麼一定要退貨？
Oh, because it doesn't really fit.
哦，因為實在不適合。
Oh, by the way, I booked the swing
哦，順便說一句，我預訂了鞦韆
kings.
國王。
Oh, that's great.
哦，那太好了。
Great, thanks.
太好了，謝謝。
But that dress, I mean, it's like, ugh,
但那件衣服，我是說，就像，呃，
it's terrible.
太可怕了。
It makes me want to just rip it
這讓我想把它撕碎
right off you.
就在你身邊。
Okay.
好的。
But you can't rip it.
但你不能撕掉它。
Well, maybe a little.
嗯，也許有一點。
Hey, guys.
嘿，夥計們。
You want to look at the song list
您想檢視歌曲列表
for the wedding?
為了婚禮？
Guys?
夥計們？
I thought you were going to be gone
我以為你會消失
all day.
一整天。
All right, what's going on?
好吧，發生什麼事了？
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
對不起，對不起。
I should probably leave you girls alone.
我也許應該讓你們女孩們靜一靜。
Yeah, laugh all you want, but in ten
是的，想笑就笑吧，但十分鐘內
minutes, we're going to have younger looking skin.
分鐘，我們就會擁有看起來更年輕的皮膚。
You know, she could use a little.
你知道，她可以用一點。
I was going to say.
我正想說。
Hold on, hold on, hold on!
堅持住，堅持住，堅持住！